{
"question": "紙",
"answer": "かみ"
},
{
"question": "鍵",
"answer": "かぎ"
},
{
"question": "雑誌",
"answer": "ざっし"
},
{
"question": "切符",
"answer": "きっぷ"
},
{
"question": "外国人",
"answer": "がいこくじん"
},
{
"question": "財布",
"answer": "さいふ"
},
{
"question": "鉛筆",
"answer": "えんぴつ"
},
{
"question": "大人",
"answer": "おとな"
},
{
"question": "塩",
"answer": "しお"
},
{
"question": "地図",
"answer": "ちず"
},
{
"question": "砂糖",
"answer": "さとう"
},
{
"question": "夏休み",
"answer": "なつやすみ"
},
{
"question": "池",
"answer": "いけ"
},
{
"question": "郵便局",
"answer": "ゆうびんきょく"
},
{
"question": "教室",
"answer": "きょうしつ"
},
{
"question": "耳",
"answer": "みみ"
},
{
"question": "切手",
"answer": "きって"
},
{
"question": "台所",
"answer": "だいどころ"
},
{
"question": "電気",
"answer": "でんき"
},
{
"question": "作文",
"answer": "さくぶん"
},
